Instructions for the worm enemy:
1.- Drag the blender file from finder to unity. And drag it to the scene. Be sure there's an Armature and a Cilinder. 
2.- For the body: select a mesh (any), then material. Drag the UV texture to the square next to the albedo. (not the droplet square). 
3.- Grab the height map and place it on the square next to the normal map, choose to correct it (a pop up shpuld appear), the hm should be purpleish now.
4.- 	set metalic to 0.495
	 set smoothness to 0.7
	set emmission to black & 0
5.- Create an animator controller (ACbody)
6.- Drag the body avatar (in the blender files) the animator in the body (in the scene). Drag ACbody to it as well.
7.- Click on the worm in the scene. Open the animator controller window. Drag the IDDLE animation first, then the scream (or whichever you want showing first). Play the game, the worm should be moving. 
8.- Click the animation. Click edit; check the box that sais loop time and loop pose. Set the beggining time to 0 and end time to 11 for SCREEM and 100 for IDDLE. 
9.- Do the same thing for the teeth*, just put them in the mouth of the worm first. Nest the teeth with the body. 
*With some differences: Put the Deafult take animation instead of the iddle